Now I've taken weakness as my ally
I can fly to the highest heights
If I would just stop here
all I've lost would lose its luster
If you were lost out somewhere
at the same time my heart is shaken
I'd have no way to find you
your kindness, or even your strength
I know...
It's time for the dawn!
My peak performance
blow straight past in a blast, yeah
You'll be left frozen with laughs
The days of pain left in the past, let's hope
As Imake foes of the world
I'm bracing myself upon shaking legs, yeah
Just keep me going for a few more steps
Now, this is the comeback, the time to awaken is now
Now, this is the comeback the time to awaken is now
What is this picture?!
Of all the ridiculous...!
I thought we told him
to remove the damned "D.", too!
No, sir, we weren't told about it!
We received the photos
from Guernica-sama of CP-0.
You will reprint them,
immediately!
Hear me? Such drivel will not be
unleashed unto the world!
But sir, we're unable to
contact the printing company...
Useless, the whole lot of them!
We must stop distribution, somehow!
What's this?
This mystical figure...!
Deliver! Deliver!
Deliver every single copy,
employees of mine!
Cipher Pol infiltrated Wano,
and no one's heard from them since!
Their final transmission:
It's Big Mom's ship!"
I'm not letting 'em cover this up!
The times are a-changin',
and that's when the truth's the most interesting!
There's nothing like good old
live entertainment!
W-What the?!
It's a special edition!
An incident?!
Hey, check this out!
"Emperors of the Sea,
Kaido and Big Mom, Defeated!"
In seemingly no time at all,
the massive headline circled the globe.
As for the trio of pirate captains
who felled the two Emperors...
...that lorded over the seas for decades...
The Government placed an exorbitant bounty
of three billion berries on each of them!
Three billion berries?!
Boss!
Wow, Captain!
Hey!
Lemme get a closer look!
Read here.
No freakin' way!
Unbelievable!
Whoa, Boss!!
Where's Kid off to now?
And with that weird look on his face...
Probably to the Flower Capital.
We got a new Emperor of the Sea, huh?
No wonder they picked them....
Hey, guys! Heard they're havin'
a feast in the capital today.
Let's join 'em!
Aye!
Just in time!
We gotta celebrate!
Let's get crazy!
Yay! Festival, festival!
We're pumped!
And there goes trouble, again...
Add cloud ear mushrooms
and chrysanthemum petals to the soup.
A plate of gisei tofu.
Abowl of flower-shaped lotus roots.
Asmall bowl of pickled vegetables...
We must not let anything happen
to our valued guests.
So we grind everything once,
heat it up, and reshape it,
then test it for poison three times...
And now, my skills
are on full display today!
Please partake of our traditional cuisine,
worthy of the Shogun himself!
Ah, what is this?
B-But why?!
None of them could wait the two hours
for the dishes to be ready.
Still, it all looks so delicious!
I appreciate your consideration!
It's quite lively out there,
wouldn't you say!
Festival, festival!
Let's play 'til we drop!
Yeah!
There's chocolate bananas
and yakisoba!
Takoyaki and grilled squid!
Cotton candy, too!
This's the best!
Everything's on the house today!
On the house!
This is my first time at a festival!
Such fun!
There's so much tasty stuff,
I can't decide what I wanna eat next!
Say, you two!
What are those?
They're called candy apples!
'Tis practically a jewel!
Beautiful!
Sweet and sour!
Wonderful flavors!
Any other fruit
wouldn't taste this good!
What're we waitin' for?!
Let's dig in!
Sho good!
Say, since you two know so much,
tell me of any
non-food stalls as well!
Awwright, leave it t'me!
When you're full
you just gotta go...
Gum-Gum Target Shooting!
Oh yeah!
Got 'im good!
You are a funny one, Luffy!
Luffy, you're not supposed
to use your hands!
Can I go again, old guy?
Nuhhh?!
It broke...
How about another try?
Okay, it's my turn!
They're in!
Oh, that was amazing!
You're pretty good, Chopper!
You ain't gonna make me happy
by complimenting me, ya jerks!
But he looks really happy...
Yeah!
You all having a great time, folks?
Yeah, all right!
Rock on, Brook!
This number is a big hit,
and it's going to light up Wano!
I'm gonna deliver to you the finest soul music,
together with the princess you all love!
That's right! It's the song
that Brother Oden loved!
"Moon Princess"!
Princess Hiyori!
What might these be?
Piqued your interest, Nico Robin?
Tengu-san!
How do you know my name?
My personal collection.
What?
Comely, are they not?
My beautiful girl kokeshi dolls!
Not particularly.
Oof!
My, how melodramatic!
You're so silly, Tengu-san.
Now that I think about it,
why keep your collection here?
This is my secret hobby room,
and the place in which I was confined for many years.
"Confined"?
I suppose you're more than
just a swordsmith, then.
Smithing is but
a mere hobby of mine.
Though it seems I've the aptitude for it.
Governing tires me so...
Who are you, really?
I?
Kozuki Sukiyakı
My name is Kozuki Sukiyaki.
What a surprise!
Does Momo-chan know?
He does not.
Nor do I intend to tell him.
But...
...our retainers may have noticed.
I am the principal culprit in allowing
Orochi to usurp our country's throne.
As such, who would I be able
to tell that I yet live?
When I barely escaped
this room with my life,
Oden was already dead,
and the Land of Wano had changed for the worse.
I considered
ritual disembowelment where I stood,
but had no choice but to hide...
...until the coming day
for the sake of my remaining mission.
And now, after what transpired since,
I owe my deepest gratitude
to all of you for everything.
I'm sure they'll all be happy to hear that.
Is that so...
Ah, Tengu-san.
There's something I'd like to talk to you about..
I believe this country possesses one of them...
The Ancient Weapon,
Pluton.
How do you know this?!
It's written on the Poneglyph
in the Kingdom of Alabasta.
And here I did not expect
anyone to know so much...
Aye, 'tis here.
Noooo, I'm the
don't-wanna-be-thin kind of guy...!
I warned ya not to test me, didn't I?!
A guy in my position can't go around
getting beat by some pirate's underlings!
The Navy don't got the manpower
to clean up this mess right now.
Still, turned out
like I thought it would...
Well, I guess you guys did okay...
Ain't the best swill, for sure...
Sheesh...
Shoulda aged it longer.
Ring, ring, ring...
Clik.
Yes, sir, this is
Hey, it's me.
Send a battleship to Wano, on the double!
What?! Oh, G-Green Bull-
And no tattlin'
to Sakazuki-san! Out.
Clik.
I like that about him, really do.
His "cut no corners" attitude.
I wanna earn his praise,
like a "Good job" or something...
By taking this brat's head, maybe...
Who's that up there?
Kay, listen up, everybody!
Ninjas, pirates, Minks, and samurai!
The king's retainers!
Yakuza, and all of Wano!
Way to put up a hell of a fight,
ye scalawags!
Good going, young man!
Make a toast!
Do it, feastmaster!
Awwright, you got it!
Luffy...
Don't tell the
whole country about me.
Why would I not?
It'd make me a hero.
And what is the matter with that?
There is no denying your victory over Kaido!
Ya big idiot!
Everyone's been waitin'
for you, Momo!
Get out of my way!
Straw Hat!
If I get rid of you here...
Jaggy!
Let's set them off!
All right! To tomorrow's food...
The hell're ya doin'?!
Here we go!
Cheers!
Make some noise!
Yeah!
I'll absolutely keep drinking to that!
party!
Let's Got that, y'all!
We're gonna drink the night away!
They're a wild bunch,
those pirates...
Honestly, who's ever heard of such
an enormous feast as this?
Hey, don't get me involved!
Oh, come on! It's a party!
ain't got a clue about
what's happening overseas...
But d'ya see this crap?!
This's why I'm here to get rid of ya!
Hwuuuuh?!
Indeed, Eustass Kid went to Luffy,
an expression of anger on his face,
for a very clear reason.
It is the herald of
the end of the old regime,
and the beginning of a new era.
Buggy, the Genius Jester...
"Blackbeard" Teach...
Red-Haired Shanks...
And Straw Hat Luffy...
These are the new emperors...
The Four Emperors of the Sea!
The festival music
sounds awfully happy...
But the Navy ain't
in the mood for that, brats...
Partytime's over...
I'm gonna bleed all of you dry...
The outside world's a mess...
I'm gonna take your head,
so just wait for me there...
Been a while...
This is my first time back here
since we said goodbye to Oden-san...
Momo and Hiyori must be
all grown up by now...
There's something here...
...that shouldn't be here.
Ms. Ninja Lady?
Something foul approaches.
It comes from outside.
Shinobu!
You both felt it as well?
Something approaches!
Take heed, all...
Luffy-dono and his comrades
are still recovering from their battle wounds.
Do not let them know about this!
So you-gara noticed, too?
We must not allow
the din of the festival to stop!
Onward!
They say "influence" is something...
...that's hard to come by...
...When you really want it.
Hey, now.
Only guy I've got business with
is Straw Hat Luffy.
Don't get in my way, samurai.
H-He is... a marine of the Navy!
The enemy Luffy-dono
and his crew faced abroad!
You bunch actually know
about the outside world, huh?
Then... d'ya know about this?
Flower Shuriken!
Shinobu!
Raizo!
Aye!
Kappa Style:
River of Retribution!
Sheesh...
What?!
Determined, aren't ya...
...ya damn samurai!
Raizo-sama!
The Celestial Dragons
are the gods of the world!
And since this country isn't
a member of the World Government,
you ain't got no rights!
I am sorry...!
Groves of Wrath!
I ate the Woods-Woods Fruit
and became a Woodsman!
Just like the seas,
the woods bear forth life!
It's the very essence of Logia!
If you're gonna be in my way,
I'll just deal with the bunch of ya permanently!
It don't matter how many people I kill in this country
'cause the law don't reach here!
You spurn us?!
How can you think so little of our people?!
Here's a lesson for ya:
Humanity's always kept some of its own down!
That's 'cause the sacrifice of a few's
necessary to make peace for the many!
Non-member countries like yours
are sacrificed for the sake of the world!
And by keepin' folks like you down,
the rest of us can go on with our lives!
Discrimination is comfort!
Don't hate me, though!
That's just the way the world works!
Stop me if ya can!
Even if it means
killin' thousands of people,
I'm gonna get my hands
on Straw Hat Luffy!
Every last word of yours...
inexcusable!
'Ey, boss!
Let's go see Luffy!
He's pretty much
a great pirate now!
Whattaguy, eh?
Whattaguy, for real!
Yow, ow, owch!
That's some strong Haki!
For twenty years,
they endured tyranny...
And only now were they fully liberated,
so I will not allow any interruption of their celebration!
Who the hell're you?!
I am Yamato, son of Kaido!
Kaido's...?
Right you are, Yamato!
Momonosuke-sama!
You will not lay your hand
upon our recovering heroes!
A dragon?!
Blast Breath!
Momonosuke-sama!
Regardless...!
Begone!
Leave the sight of the capital!
Do not cause my people anguish!
I promised my people
there would be no more!
Strange...
A pink dragon?
I've never heard of
such a Devil Fruit power!
You're in my way!
Momonosuke-kun!
Yamato!
You must not fight!
Eh?
We're gonna be inside
Wano's borders soon!
H-Hey!
Hold off on going ashore...
I'm...
...not really ready to see Usopp...
Yeah... And I bet that
brat Kid's still there, too!
He came tryin' to pick a fight
with us just the other day!
Ah, pipe down!
The Boss'll decide what we're doin'.
This is...
That's...
Red-Haired's ship!
Pain in my ass...
We're going!
Fire! Keep Red-Haired away!
What's he doing?!
What does he want?!
There's no treasure on this ship!
There's just one Devil Fruit...
All it does is turn you into rubber!
I'mma prove it to ya!
Uh-huh, go on then!
Owwieee!
You dunce!
What the hellre you doing?!
Hey, wait, Luffy.
His arm stretched!
The heck's going on?!
Scram.
I thought you were a man!
But... Shanks...!
Your arm!
Guess all our bosses know
Straw Hat Luffy personally...
They say Straw Hat Luffy's...
I heard he's outta control,
a totally savage monster of an ape...!
Got no intention of seeing Luffy.
What?!
Think about what's going on
in our territories these days.
That man going on about
being Luffy's henchman, Barto...
Barto... whatshisface?
He burned our Jolly Roger
and changed it to Luffy's...
He's the future Pirate King,
Luffy-senpai!
This is his crew's sticker!
This island's the territory of
Shanks of the Four Emperors!
Say whuh?
One o' the Four Emperors?!
I dun give a crap!
If we just let it slide...
I'd lose people's trust in me.
Well, that's true...
But still...!
Aw, c'mon, Boss!
I wanna see him!
Me, too!
We can't allow the Revolutionary Army
to run around unchecked, Red Hound!
I know that already,
but I don't got the troops to deploy.
Sabo...
He's a hero to the world now!
Eight hundred years ago,
the World Government was created by twenty founders.
Of their descendants, only Nefertari Cobra
attended the Reverie this year.
That's why his murder had
significance to the Revolutionary Army!
A few hours before that, in the Land of the Gods
where the Celestial Dragons live,
they destroyed the Hoof of the Celestial Dragon,
the symbol of the World Nobles, and declared war!
Led by Admirals Green Bull and Wisteria Tiger,
the Navy fought back, but the outcome...
Former Revolutionary Army soldier and
Celestial Dragon slave...
...Bartholomew Kuma was freed,
and they all escaped!
It must've been difficult for the Admirals
to fight in the Land of the Gods.
You don't need to
make excuses for them.
And what of Princess Vivi's disappearance?
This occurred around the same time as Cobra's murder...
Both cases currently under investigation,
along with any connection between them.
Alabasta's got to be
a complete mess.
King Cobra's ship
is still at the Red Port...
The situation dictates
they can't leave for home.
Can we close the case
on the attempted murder of Saint Charlos?
In regard to Saint Myosgard
excusing the assailants,
they're still deliberating
in the Land of the Gods.
The Holy Knights intervened,
and it's getting complicated.
Leave them to it!
People are excited, thinking that
Sabo was behind all these incidents!
The lands that were a part of the recent
Eight-Nation Revolution,
and anywhere around the world
where there's sparks of rebellion,
have started worshipping him like a god!
They're calling him
the "Flame Emperor"!
His popularity now exceeds...
...that of "Insurgent Serpent" Dragon,
leader of the Revolutionary Army!
And to top it all off, his younger brother,
Straw Hat Luffy, is now one of the Four Emperors.
In the pirate world,
the Flame Emperor's brother
did away with the old guard!
Now, a new era is upon us!
For cryin' out loud...
Hell of a time I picked
to become the Fleet Admiral...
But no matter how they come at me,
I'm gonna send hell right back at 'em!
Hey, Beck...
Think it's about time
we take it for ourselves...
The One Piece!
"Time's up'
Someone said again, with a laugh
Fine then, hide-and-seek playtime...
...is over
Let's go, come on (We can see it soon)
Let your heart beat out
and things will change (We can see it soon)
Grow strong, you have time
Lift up that dream
The overflowing loneliness can't sustain me alone
We were so free in our younger days
What a dumb dream
...to live
Shining a light on uncharted ways
Get on our feet and try
Let's see the ends of the world together
Together, we can go and fly